<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>TEMPLATE</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on TEMPLATE</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-au</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>04: binary exploitation</title><link>/week04/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/week04/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ll get started at 13:05 binary exploitation week04 disclaimer many of the tools and techniques discussed in these sessions could be used against real websites/applications don&amp;rsquo;t do that acknowledgement of country We begin by acknowledging the Traditional Custodians of the land on which we meet, and pay our respects to their Elders past and present. We extend that arespect to Aboriginal and Torres Strait Islander peoples here today. what will we cover this session buffers overflows shellcode return-oriented programming buffer overflows Q: what happens if you write more content into a buffer than it can store?</description></item><item><title>05: forensics</title><link>/week05/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/week05/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ll get started at 13:05 Digital Forensics &amp;amp; Incident Response Week05 disclaimer many of the tools and techniques discussed in these sessions could be used against real websites/applications don&amp;rsquo;t do that acknowledgement of country We begin by acknowledging the Traditional Custodians of the land on which we meet, and pay our respects to their Elders past and present. We extend that arespect to Aboriginal and Torres Strait Islander peoples here today.</description></item><item><title>06: reverse engineering</title><link>/week06/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/week06/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ll get started at 13:05 TODO Week06 disclaimer many of the tools and techniques discussed in these sessions could be used against real websites/applications don&amp;rsquo;t do that acknowledgement of country We begin by acknowledging the Traditional Custodians of the land on which we meet, and pay our respects to their Elders past and present. We extend that respect to Aboriginal and Torres Strait Islander peoples here today. what will we cover this session The CTF static analysis dynamic analysis CTF 9am 11/09 - 10pm 15/09 join discord prizes: prezzee vouchers web the bulk of the challenges as these are the most natural and fun a mix of client-side and server-side vulnerabilities you get a link to a website, you need to exploit it to (rce, session fixation?</description></item><item><title>ctfs &amp;&amp; recon</title><link>/week01/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/week01/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ll get started at 13:05 what is a ctf &amp;amp;&amp;amp; recon week01 disclaimer many of the tools and techniques discussed in these sessions could be used against real applications don&amp;rsquo;t do that acknowledgement of country We begin by acknowledging the Traditional Custodians of the land on which we meet, and pay our respects to their Elders past and present. We extend that arespect to Aboriginal and Torres Strait Islander peoples here today.</description></item><item><title>Week02</title><link>/week02/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/week02/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ll get started at 13:05 client-side exploitation week02 disclaimer many of the tools and techniques discussed in these sessions could be used against real applications don&amp;rsquo;t do that acknowledgement of country We begin by acknowledging the Traditional Custodians of the land on which we meet, and pay our respects to their Elders past and present. We extend that arespect to Aboriginal and Torres Strait Islander peoples here today. Client-side injection HTML Injection XSS CSRF Clickjacking HTML injection Browsers just render the DOM How would it know if tags are user-supplied or server-supplied what if our input was just &amp;lt;s&amp;gt;?</description></item><item><title>week03: serverside</title><link>/week03/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/week03/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ll get started at 13:05 server-side exploitation week03 disclaimer many of the tools and techniques discussed in these sessions could be used against real applications dont do that acknowledgement of country We begin by acknowledging the Traditional Custodians of the land on which we meet, and pay our respects to their Elders past and present. We extend that arespect to Aboriginal and Torres Strait Islander peoples here today. housekeeping did anyone try out any of the challenges?</description></item></channel></rss>